# Carmen Ng

#### Web Developer

An adaptable and motivated individual with a strong understanding of visual communications currently working as a Solutions Developer. Over 3 years of web development experience has allowed me to develop strong analytical and problem solving skills. I am eager to continue learning new skills and gain more experience in various areas and languages as I am always striving for self improvement, both professionally and personally.

carmenng.media@gmail.com

Hong Kong

in linkedin.com/in/carng

📘 🛮 Available via Email

nightlightvisuals.com

github.com/CarNg

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### **Solutions Developer**

PCCW Solutions

04/2017 - Present Hong Kong

- Redesign and develop frontend (JSP, JavaScript, jQuery and CSS) for clients' exisiting ERP systems.
- Work directly with BAs to design and develop more user friendly flows and enhancements.
- API connection to existing Oracle E-Business ERP (Java).

### **Full Stack Developer**

RT-Technology Ideas Holding Ltd. &

04/2016 - 03/2017 Hong Kong

RT-Technology is behind BabyPOS POS system. In addition to POS products, they also provide services in web design & development and SEO optimisation.

- Develop and manage the POS system's responsive web platform.
- Connect the POS system's API to clients' online shops' API allowing live updates between the two.
- Design and develop clients' websites and online shops.
- Design and develop internal sites that were used by sales team and for marketing purposes.

Contact: Raymond Tse - raymond@babypos.hk

### Game Design Intern

Simteractive Ltd.

04/2015 – 10/2015 Dublin, Ireland Simteractive is a Dublin-based video game developer, specialising in F2P mobile games.

 Worked on Simteractive's debut iOS release - Eden Isle: Resort Paradise

Contact: Elaine Reynolds - elaine@simteractive.com

# **EDUCATION**

### **MSc in Creative Digital Media**

Dublin Institute of Technology

09/2013 - 02/2015 First Class Honours

# BA (Hons) Journalism and Visual Media

Griffith College Dublin

09/2009 - 07/2012 First Class Honours

### **SKILLS**

HTML5		
CSS3	• • • • •	
JavaScript		)
Reactjs		)
jQuery		)
Bootstrap		)

### **PERSONAL PROJECTS**

Night Light Visuals (2015 - Present)

 Night Light Visuals is my personal branding and portfolio site for my previous and current projects. The website is built using React\_js

### This Time Around (02/2014 - 02/2015)

 'This Time Around' is an interactive fiction/exploration game developed as a MSc final project. My responsibilities included game design (mechanics & aesthetics), narrative creation, programming using C# in Unity3D, sound design, QA, testing with users and analysing results, marketing the game, write a full report detailing the process of game development from research to final product.

# **ACHIEVEMENTS**

#### Best Game Script Nominee (06/2018)

Nominated for a Writers' Guild of Ireland ZeBBie Award in Best Game Script as a co-writer of Simteractive's Eden Isle: Resort Paradise

### **LANGUAGES**

### **INTERESTS**

Bouldering Boxing Videography Gaming

Music Travelling